[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Yorker"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "I take it you enjoyed the Super Bowl yesterday?", "question_tokens": ["I", "take", "it", "you", "enjoyed", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "yesterday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Yes, well, of course, I'm a Giants fan, being a New Yorker.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "Giants", "fan", ",", "being", "a", "New", "Yorker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Columbia"], "LOCATION": ["New Yorker"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Who do you think is going to win as things stand?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "is", "going", "to", "win", "as", "things", "stand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, if you want to keep using that analogy to a fairly well, of course, Obama is sort of a New Yorker because he did time at Columbia.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "want", "to", "keep", "using", "that", "analogy", "to", "a", "fairly", "well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "Obama", "is", "sort", "of", "a", "New", "Yorker", "because", "he", "did", "time", "at", "Columbia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Do you see any other of the Republican candidates seriously threatening Romney at this stage?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "any", "other", "of", "the", "Republican", "candidates", "seriously", "threatening", "Romney", "at", "this", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What's the real man like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "real", "man", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "You know, according to all accounts, including people who are essentially friendly to him, he is a very reserved guy, whose main passions are his family and his Mormon faith, in which he's been very active not just as a parishioner but as a leader and lay official.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "according", "to", "all", "accounts", ",", "including", "people", "who", "are", "essentially", "friendly", "to", "him", ",", "he", "is", "a", "very", "reserved", "guy", ",", "whose", "main", "passions", "are", "his", "family", "and", "his", "Mormon", "faith", ",", "in", "which", "he", "'s", "been", "very", "active", "not", "just", "as", "a", "parishioner", "but", "as", "a", "leader", "and", "lay", "official", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What do you think as an overview about America's foreign policy going forward?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "as", "an", "overview", "about", "America", "'s", "foreign", "policy", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, I think that Obama has been a very good steward and done all the things you said and managed the Libya situation, which he took a lot of heat from both the left and the right, quite well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "Obama", "has", "been", "a", "very", "good", "steward", "and", "done", "all", "the", "things", "you", "said", "and", "managed", "the", "Libya", "situation", ",", "which", "he", "took", "a", "lot", "of", "heat", "from", "both", "the", "left", "and", "the", "right", ",", "quite", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "I mean this election will be fought and won or lost on jobs and the economy, won't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "this", "election", "will", "be", "fought", "and", "won", "or", "lost", "on", "jobs", "and", "the", "economy", ",", "wo", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "And final question, Frank, I men do you think that if Barack Obama wins the election, that if he gets to that point, he will be a better president in the second term than he's been in the first term?", "question_tokens": ["And", "final", "question", ",", "Frank", ",", "I", "men", "do", "you", "think", "that", "if", "Barack", "Obama", "wins", "the", "election", ",", "that", "if", "he", "gets", "to", "that", "point", ",", "he", "will", "be", "a", "better", "president", "in", "the", "second", "term", "than", "he", "'s", "been", "in", "the", "first", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "about", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I just hoped that it was an awful rumor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "hoped", "that", "it", "was", "an", "awful", "rumor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Have you ever had any doubt that Josh Powell was responsible for Susan's death?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "had", "any", "doubt", "that", "Josh", "Powell", "was", "responsible", "for", "Susan", "'s", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I had no doubt whatsoever but I don't believe he acted alone.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "no", "doubt", "whatsoever", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "he", "acted", "alone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh Powell", "Susan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "You think there's somebody else out there that was an accomplice?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "there", "'s", "somebody", "else", "out", "there", "that", "was", "an", "accomplice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I do, because I know Josh and I know that he likes to make big grandiose plans and talk big but it always takes somebody else pushing him to carry things out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "because", "I", "know", "Josh", "and", "I", "know", "that", "he", "likes", "to", "make", "big", "grandiose", "plans", "and", "talk", "big", "but", "it", "always", "takes", "somebody", "else", "pushing", "him", "to", "carry", "things", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "And how do you feel about the fact that these boys, through a court ruling, had to be returned to him, given his obviously very confused state of mind?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "these", "boys", ",", "through", "a", "court", "ruling", ",", "had", "to", "be", "returned", "to", "him", ",", "given", "his", "obviously", "very", "confused", "state", "of", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I'm upset and I'm angry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "upset", "and", "I", "'m", "angry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Utah"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Or was there any sign that something awful would happen?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "there", "any", "sign", "that", "something", "awful", "would", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "When they first moved to Utah about five years before she disappeared, they were pretty affectionate, they were still a kind of -- in the newlywed stage.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "they", "first", "moved", "to", "Utah", "about", "five", "years", "before", "she", "disappeared", ",", "they", "were", "pretty", "affectionate", ",", "they", "were", "still", "a", "kind", "of", "--", "in", "the", "newlywed", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "He started to talk more and more to his father, Steve Powell, on the phone and to get more antagonist stick and controlling towards Susan?", "question_tokens": ["He", "started", "to", "talk", "more", "and", "more", "to", "his", "father", ",", "Steve", "Powell", ",", "on", "the", "phone", "and", "to", "get", "more", "antagonist", "stick", "and", "controlling", "towards", "Susan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "And there was this bizarre twist where the father-in-law began to make all these claims about Susan being flirtatious with him and so on.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "there", "was", "this", "bizarre", "twist", "where", "the", "father-in-law", "began", "to", "make", "all", "these", "claims", "about", "Susan", "being", "flirtatious", "with", "him", "and", "so", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Powell", "Susan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan"], "LOCATION": ["Utah"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What did you think when you heard all that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "when", "you", "heard", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I already knew it all because Susan had already told me many times over the years all about the fact that her father tried to hit on her, that he was obsessed with her, and that he was in love with her, that she couldn't stand him and that they moved to Utah to get away with him -- get away from him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "already", "knew", "it", "all", "because", "Susan", "had", "already", "told", "me", "many", "times", "over", "the", "years", "all", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "her", "father", "tried", "to", "hit", "on", "her", ",", "that", "he", "was", "obsessed", "with", "her", ",", "and", "that", "he", "was", "in", "love", "with", "her", ",", "that", "she", "could", "n't", "stand", "him", "and", "that", "they", "moved", "to", "Utah", "to", "get", "away", "with", "him", "--", "get", "away", "from", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Do you think we ever will?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "we", "ever", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I do think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "What is the mood in the community?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "mood", "in", "the", "community", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Everyone is in shock.", "answer_tokens": ["Everyone", "is", "in", "shock", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh", "Susan"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "What's been his reaction to this shocking turn of events?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "his", "reaction", "to", "this", "shocking", "turn", "of", "events", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "He and Josh were pretty good friends up until about a year or two before Susan disappeared.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "and", "Josh", "were", "pretty", "good", "friends", "up", "until", "about", "a", "year", "or", "two", "before", "Susan", "disappeared", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Have you had any contact with the family?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "any", "contact", "with", "the", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I called Susan's father yesterday after a reporter told me what had happened or rumors what had happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "called", "Susan", "'s", "father", "yesterday", "after", "a", "reporter", "told", "me", "what", "had", "happened", "or", "rumors", "what", "had", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "You are a Parisian?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "a", "Parisian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "From France?", "question_tokens": ["From", "France", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "How are you feeling?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I'm feeling quite good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "feeling", "quite", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Is Hollywood stampeding to your door?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Hollywood", "stampeding", "to", "your", "door", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "It doesn't get bigger, does it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "get", "bigger", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "You know, I'm -- I'm OK.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "'m", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Have you prepared an Oscar winning speech?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "prepared", "an", "Oscar", "winning", "speech", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "But what happens when a film becomes this huge, massive hit and you're all starting to think you may win an Oscar?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "happens", "when", "a", "film", "becomes", "this", "huge", ",", "massive", "hit", "and", "you", "'re", "all", "starting", "to", "think", "you", "may", "win", "an", "Oscar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "You want to win, though, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "win", ",", "though", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I really want to win, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "want", "to", "win", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "But when you first heard from Michel, I've got a great idea, I'm going to put you in a silent film -- be honest, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "first", "heard", "from", "Michel", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "a", "great", "idea", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "put", "you", "in", "a", "silent", "film", "--", "be", "honest", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "VB", "JJS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I have to be honest, I said, great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "be", "honest", ",", "I", "said", ",", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Now, on the subject of love, one of my favorite questions I ask most of my guests -- and it's very appropriate in your case -- is how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "on", "the", "subject", "of", "love", ",", "one", "of", "my", "favorite", "questions", "I", "ask", "most", "of", "my", "guests", "--", "and", "it", "'s", "very", "appropriate", "in", "your", "case", "--", "is", "how", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Uhmm --", "answer_tokens": ["Uhmm", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Properly?", "question_tokens": ["Properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Let's just use your analogy, when the arrow goes into the heart.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "just", "use", "your", "analogy", ",", "when", "the", "arrow", "goes", "into", "the", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "To Michel?", "question_tokens": ["To", "Michel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "The love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["The", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "He's definitely the man of my life, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "definitely", "the", "man", "of", "my", "life", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "What makes him so special?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "him", "so", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "He's very smart and he doesn't take him seriously and that's all I love about him.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "very", "smart", "and", "he", "does", "n't", "take", "him", "seriously", "and", "that", "'s", "all", "I", "love", "about", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "The dog?", "question_tokens": ["The", "dog", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "EJO: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["EJO", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "He doesn't really -- he's not a huge fan of dogs.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "really", "--", "he", "'s", "not", "a", "huge", "fan", "of", "dogs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "So you make him have this dog that he just doesn't like?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "make", "him", "have", "this", "dog", "that", "he", "just", "does", "n't", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I mean, he loves the dog in the movie and he loves the character of the dog.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "he", "loves", "the", "dog", "in", "the", "movie", "and", "he", "loves", "the", "character", "of", "the", "dog", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "So you've put this poor guy through hell?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "put", "this", "poor", "guy", "through", "hell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Yes, poor guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "poor", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "I mean, this is a bit of a downward grade here, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "this", "is", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "downward", "grade", "here", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "No, actually, it's the completion of a circle, because the first film I ever did was \"Murder By Death\" and I played a chauffeur.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "actually", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "completion", "of", "a", "circle", ",", "because", "the", "first", "film", "I", "ever", "did", "was", "``", "Murder", "By", "Death", "''", "and", "I", "played", "a", "chauffeur", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Do you turn to your agent and manager and go, am I going crazy here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "turn", "to", "your", "agent", "and", "manager", "and", "go", ",", "am", "I", "going", "crazy", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "No, because, actually, when you hear what it is, a silent movie, black and white, an unknown director, to us, two unknown French actors and you say, well, that sounds like a stupid idea.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", ",", "actually", ",", "when", "you", "hear", "what", "it", "is", ",", "a", "silent", "movie", ",", "black", "and", "white", ",", "an", "unknown", "director", ",", "to", "us", ",", "two", "unknown", "French", "actors", "and", "you", "say", ",", "well", ",", "that", "sounds", "like", "a", "stupid", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Well, he saw the magic, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "saw", "the", "magic", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes, sure he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sure", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "But for you, when you saw that narrative, how did it make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["But", "for", "you", ",", "when", "you", "saw", "that", "narrative", ",", "how", "did", "it", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I mean, certainly, yes, I could relate to it a bit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "certainly", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "could", "relate", "to", "it", "a", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", ":", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 589, "question": "So he's a really offensive dog, as well?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "'s", "a", "really", "offensive", "dog", ",", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "I mean, he's -- he's a big black no -- no especially elegant with a --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "he", "'s", "--", "he", "'s", "a", "big", "black", "no", "--", "no", "especially", "elegant", "with", "a", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "ORGAN: -- what about me asking you the same question I asked your wife, which is how many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "--", "what", "about", "me", "asking", "you", "the", "same", "question", "I", "asked", "your", "wife", ",", "which", "is", "how", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "-- fall in love about every week, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["--", "fall", "in", "love", "about", "every", "week", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "She's really the -- the -- the -- the lead actress of my -- of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "really", "the", "--", "the", "--", "the", "--", "the", "lead", "actress", "of", "my", "--", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Is it -- is it, in realism, going to actually produce a new birth to silent films or not?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "it", ",", "in", "realism", ",", "going", "to", "actually", "produce", "a", "new", "birth", "to", "silent", "films", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I wouldn't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michel"]}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "But I would do another silent film if Michel directed it.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "would", "do", "another", "silent", "film", "if", "Michel", "directed", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Yes, because this silent film works because of his vision and his conception and his artistry, his mastery, his humanity.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "this", "silent", "film", "works", "because", "of", "his", "vision", "and", "his", "conception", "and", "his", "artistry", ",", "his", "mastery", ",", "his", "humanity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]